<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Non Technical on purpleidea.com</title>
    <link>https://purpleidea.com/categories/non-technical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Non Technical on purpleidea.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 06:27:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://purpleidea.com/categories/non-technical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Red Hat</title>
      <link>https://purpleidea.com/blog/2018/04/04/leaving-redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 06:27:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://purpleidea.com/blog/2018/04/04/leaving-redhat/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent about four years at Red Hat, and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to move on&amp;hellip;
TL;DR: had to leave Red Hat and start Patreon to fund mgmt.
What follows is a bit of historical rambling, and some forward looking statements.
Retrospective:
Long-time readers of my blog will know that I was very active in the puppet ecosystem for many years. I learned a lot while writing puppet code, and while building some of my outrageous puppet hacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://purpleidea.com/blog/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 09:18:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://purpleidea.com/blog/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello! This is a new version of my website and blog. If you experience any issues, please let me know!
Happy Hacking, James</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copyleft is Dead. Long live Copyleft!</title>
      <link>https://purpleidea.com/blog/2017/10/17/copyleft-is-dead-long-live-copyleft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 21:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://purpleidea.com/blog/2017/10/17/copyleft-is-dead-long-live-copyleft/</guid>
      <description>As you may have noticed, we recently re-licensed mgmt from the AGPL (Affero General Public License) to the regular GPL. This is a post explaining the decision and which hopefully includes some insights at the intersection of technology and legal issues.
Disclaimer:
I am not a lawyer, and these are not necessarily the opinions of my employer. I think I&amp;rsquo;m knowledgeable in this area, but I&amp;rsquo;m happy to be corrected in the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working at RedHat</title>
      <link>https://purpleidea.com/blog/2014/04/02/working-at-redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 14:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://purpleidea.com/blog/2014/04/02/working-at-redhat/</guid>
      <description>So this happened:
 James just James at RedHat headquarters in North Carolina wearing his new red hat.RedHat made me an offer, and I am happy to say that I have just started this week!
I am proud to have joined a company that employs many of the worlds foremost, highly professional and clever hackers. It is indubitably the best Free Software [1] / Open Source company out there, and they ship some of the greatest and most elegant software available.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>